(YELLS)
Got you ! Broken arm.
Boom ! Boom ! Boom !
Broken nose! Boom ! Boom !
Boom ! Broken nose!
Gonna flip you.
Once a year, Dwight holds
a seminar updating us
on the newest developments
in the world of karate.
Because,
as we all know,
the one thing
that thousand-year-old
martial arts do all the time
is change.
How can l pose
this to you in
a relatable way?
You are all members
of the Yakuza,
and you happen to be
visiting the Lackawanna
Trolley Museum,
and you are attacked
by Triads.
How can you hold them off
until your clan arrives?
You cannot go wrong
with a throat punch.
(YELLS)
Okay, so there's
no defense for that.
Good to know.
No, there is
a defense for that.
Let me demonstrate.
Someone attack me.
Kevin, go!
No way.
Last time, you pulled
my pants down,
and then you
tried to choke me
with my shoelace.
False. l did choke you
with your shoelace.
Now come at me!
Okay, with all due respect
to everyone here,
l think the most
worthy opponent
of you is you.
That is correct,
unless there happen
to be measles present.
So let's just say that
Dwight has come at you
with the throat punch.
Now, how would you, Dwight,
defend against it?
Easy. Allow me
to demonstrate.
l am attacking myself
with a throat punch.
Here it comes.
Block. Grasp wrist as such.
And what if
he comes at you
with the other hand?
Because he does have two.
Good point.
Second throat punch.
Absorb the blow.
Groin punch.
Hit, block,
elbow to the gut!
Uh-oh ! Up to the nose!
No, you're not!
(SCREAMS lN PAlN)
Oh, my God,
he's making you
look like such a fool.
He really is,
but not for long.
Ow! God ! lnstep!
Not again !
(EXCLAlMlNG)
You let go!
l can't hold on !
You two are so
evenly matched,
l don't know how one of you
is gonna get the upper hand.
The important thing
to remember, Jim,
we always have
what is called the
element of surprise.
(SCREAMS lN PAlN)
But l would say
my favorite art form
is a tie between
sculpting and
stand-up comedy.
l did stand-up comedy once.
You did?
Yeah, l killed.
That sounds like
it was hilarious.
lt was hilarious.
DWlGHT: Michael?
Yes?
What is the meaning
of this e-mail that
everyone got?
You'll have to be
more specific, Dwight.
l get like
eight e-mails a day.
This one.
"From David Wallace
to all Dunder Mifflin."
Whoo-hoo! Shout-out.
"Hello, everyone.
l'm sure you've seen
the item in the JournaI.
"Just want to stress,
it's all conjecture.
"lf there's
any concrete news,
you will know ASAP."
Erin, do we have
the Journal?
Your "feelings journal"?
You told me to put it
in the time capsule.
Did you?
Michael,
he means The WaII Street
JournaI online.
Oh, "The wall."
l found the article.
"On a day marked by panicked
corporate board meetings,
"one that is
relatively unsurprising
is Dunder Mifflin's.
"lt is rumored that
they will recommend. . ."
And the article cuts off.
lt's $1 .99 to
finish the article.
l wonder what
it was gonna say.
Are you serious?
l got it, l got it. Oh !
Tuna beat me to it.
"lt is rumored that
they will recommend
declaring bankruptcy?"
No, no. That doesn't
make any sense.
Oh, Lord, we're all
gonna lose our jobs.
Not necessarily.
Bankruptcy could
mean a lot of things.
Maybe they're
just restructuring
to get out of debt.
Right.
Oh, that sounds awful.
Or it could mean
the end of Dunder Mifflin.
Oh, God ! Well, that's
an interesting theory.
You know what?
You can all have
jobs at Schrute Farms
as human scarecrows.
lt doesn't pay much
and you can't unionize.
WOMAN OVER PHONE:
l'm sorry, Michael.
David's in a meeting.
Ah, well, maybe you
should spy on him.
(SNlCKERS)
Oh, my God !
Wouldn't that be hilarious?
I'II just have him
caII you back
when he's free.
Okay, okay. Good.
l'll catch you on
the flippity-flip. Bye!
He's busy.
Call me back when he's free.
(MlCHAEL RETCHlNG)
Michael, are you okay?
Did you throw up in there?
No, just pooping.
You know how l be.
But it smells like
throw-up in here.
Crazy world,
lot of smells.
You guys, what if this
is our last day at work?
What if we never see
each other ever again?
l like Erin.
There, l said it.
l was kind of hoping
she would ask me out,
but things have not
panned out on that front,
so, it's time
for the Nard-Dog
to take matters
into his own paws.
(ALL MURMURlNG)
(SlNGlNG)
Everything is gonna
We have to do something,
because people are
losing it out there,
wondering what's
gonna happen.
Okay, we need some
sort of distraction
for everybody.
ls there anything new
on YouTube?
Michael. . .
Doesn't even need
to be good. Oh, God !
l can't think.
l need more Mullins.
Listen, Wallace said
these were just rumors,
right?
So we have no reason to
think that the company's
anything but fine.
So if we just go on
with our work,
you and me,
they'll follow along.
Monkey see, monkey do.
That's it.
Monkey pee all over you.
That rhymes.
So what have we
on the docket today?
We have a monthly
staff meeting.
All right!
Let's conference room it up!
Here's the deal, guys.
There is no new
information as of yet,
so l suggest we all
just keep working.
Sure, l'm a little nervous,
but doing our work
will make us feel better.
l only slack off
when things are good.
Customers have to
use the coupon code
from the website.
And as of now,
there is no
differentiation
between
the letter O
and the zero,
but we are working on that.
Stay tuned for that.
He needs me.
Seat-save infinity.
Okay, great.
Also. . .
Oh, God ! What?
Oh, my God.
What?
Michael, what happened?
PAM: ls there news?
There has been a murder!
What?
There's been a murder
in Savannah.
MlCHAEL: Games have the
power to distract peopIe
from stressful situations.
Battleship got me through
my parents' divorce.
Operation got me
through my vasectomy,
i.e. , "My Operation."
l don't think
l would have been
able to endure my
break-up with Holly
had it not been
for Toss Across.
"Belles, Bourbon, and Bullets,
a murder mystery
dinner party game."
lt is so much fun.
Everybody plays a character,
we go around the room,
we try to figure out
who did it.
Hey, l'm wondering if
this is a terrible idea.
This is my call, Jim.
Big picture stuff.
lt's about murder.
l thought we agreed
that we wouldn't do
things like this.
Tube City.
You owe me one.
Co-managing is
a give and take.
You have to
pick your battles.
One of the battles
that l picked
was to stop Michael
from running plastic tubes
all over the office
and pIacing hamsters
inside of them.
He was gonna caII it
Tube City.
So, yes,
l do owe him one. . .
MAN: August 5th, 1 955.
It's a sad day
down here in Savannah.
LocaI magnate BiII Bourbon
was kiIIed Iast night,
and aII y'aII have
congregated tonight
for a meal
to celebrate Bill
as he passes on
to his great reward.
But you're not just here
to pay your respects.
You have to figure out which
of y'aII is the no-account
scoundrel who killed him.
This is ridiculous.
There will be food.
You leave,
you do not get food.
What kind of food?
Sandwich platters.
l'm in.
Baby carrots.
Okay, here are your
character cards.
Take one, pass it down.
Here is your prop box.
Some of your characters
will have props.
Now, on your character card,
it tells you who you are
and what your alibi is.
Everything else is
up to your imagination.
So if you talk slowly
in real life,
your character could, say,
have been kicked in
the head by a horse.
Cool. l'll try it.
Okay. Use your
imaginations.
Who did you get?
"Naughty Nellie Nutmeg,
"a vivacious young socialite
with a penchant for scandal."
BOTH: Ooh !
Saucy.
How about you?
"Nathaniel Nutmeg,
the local bartender
and Nellie's brother."
Michael, l don't like
this game. lt's scary.
lt's not scary.
l don't like
my character.
Who are you?
"Voodoo Mama Juju,
the witch doctor of
the Savannah swamps."
l'm not comfortable
with this.
Well, how do you
think l feel?
l mean, l have to play
"Caleb Crawdad,"
handsome playboy.
Every night
a different woman,
being ogled,
having to hug and kiss
and spoon.
l make them
feel beautiful.
(lN SOUTHERN ACCENT)
Well, well, well !
What is this contraption,
l do declare?
lt's my BlackBerry, Michael.
l'm trying to get updates
on the company.
Who's Michael?
l'm Caleb Crawdad,
l do declare.
You don't have
to keep saying,
"l do declare,"
anytime you say something,
it means you're declaring.
That is the way
Southern people talk.
And what designing woman
are you basing that on?
Delta Burke, l do declare.
Now, shall we get
to the mystery?
l'll go.
"My name is Deborah Utante,
Deb for short."
That's clever.
Debutante.
"Bill Bourbon
was my uncle.
"l would have
never hurt him any more
than l'd hurt a June bug."
Nice accent.
You sound like
Forrest Gump.
l do not.
Well, you do, actually.
You got this kind of
like Florida Panhandle
thing going,
whereas what you
really want is more
of a Savannah accent,
which is more like
molasses just sort of
spilling out of your mouth.
Oh, now do
the Swedish Chef.
l'm not familiar.
What province is he from?
He lives on Sesame Street,
dumbass.
You know, l think
l'm supposed to say
something to Pam,
l mean, Deb. Okay.
"l overheard you asking
the butler where
the pistol was kept."
(GASPS)
Wait a minute.
l'm the butler. What,
you were listening in
on that?
Oh, you rich people,
you think you can do
whatever you want
to the servant class!
No, no, no.
Don't turn this
into a political thing.
l will poison your food.
l reckon l got
something to say
to Miss Beatrix Bourbon,
if she don't mind.
Ooh, doggy!
We got a party now!
l do believe that
the game is a big hit.
People are really
diving into their
characters.
Y'all. . .
l made a mistake.
Sorry, l'm late, boss.
What's going on?
(lN SOUTHERN ACCENT) Sir,
there has been a murder,
and you are a suspect.
Okay. Hang on just a second.
Let me settle in,
and l'll be right back.
Very good ! Very good !
Now, no one was there
in the wine cellar.
(TlRES SQUEALlNG)
(lN SOUTHERN ACCENT)
Hey there, young lady.
Hello.
l would be remiss
if l did not ask
the pretty young lady
out on a date
for this weekend.
(lN SOUTHERN ACCENT)
Sounds like a plan, sugar.
All right!
A plan it is.
(BOTH CHUCKLlNG)
Voodoo Mama Juju,
explain your dalliance
with the dark arts.
lt's not my fault.
l was exposed
to Harry Potter.
l know you did it!
l know she didn't do it.
lt's never the person
you most suspect.
lt's also never
the person you
least suspect,
since anyone with
half a brain would
suspect them the most.
Therefore,
l know the killer
to be Phyllis,
a.k.a. Beatrix Bourbon,
the person l most
medium suspect.
Do you want to go out
on a date with me?
We can make out
by the horses.
Well, you know
old Nellie is always up
for a romp in the hay.
How about
a threesome?
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
My boudoir's always open.
Nice.
l'm a little worried
l might have asked out
Naughty Nellie and not Erin.
Which would be
a whole lot
less appealing,
because Naughty Nellie
says yes to everyone,
and she might be
a murderer.
Follow before. . .
l just got an e-mail
from corporate,
specifically for Accounting,
to stop all payments
to our vendors.
What does that mean?
Well, maybe nothing,
but it could be a problem
with liquidity. . .
Whoa! What's this
strange Yankee accent
coming out of
your mouth, son?
This here is Savannah.
Phyllis. . .
(lN SOUTHERN ACCENT)
This. . . Plan. . .
This plantation,
we're running low
on greenbacks,
and we're having problems
paying the people
who give us the seeds
and the dirt.
We can't pay them.
Michael, l can't. . .
Basically, it could
mean a lot of things,
but it is unprecedented,
so it's cause for concern.
Okay, l'm going back
to work.
No. No, no, no.
No. No, no.
l'm gonna skip forward
to a really big clue.
Here we go.
MAN: WeII, by now, you
figured out that oId Beatrix
Bourbon was the killer.
PAM: What?
Michael, l was
doing so well.
Are you going to
believe that?
That is a. . .
That's a misdirection.
We still don't know
who the murderer is.
Nellie Nutmeg,
come back in here!
l can't do this myself.
Voodoo Mama Juju.
What am l gonna do?
Okay, so corporate is
still in their meeting.
That could be
a good sign.
Hey, everyone,
Kevin's gonna give us
his take on the situation.
Let's listen up.
All right, guys,
it's a workday,
and you guys work here,
so let's go
do some work.
Now, Jim telling us
all to work,
l think that is
a very good sign.
Don't just say things.
Oh, good, Michael.
Listen, l wrote up
those sales targets. . .
l do believe
you have me mistaken.
My name is Caleb Crawdad.
Y'all skedaddled way
too soon. We need to
reopen this case.
No, you're not
re-opening the case.
The case is closed.
No, it ain't.
Frankly,
l'm not surprised.
A lot of the evidence
seemed to be based on puns.
l was just thinking about
Weekend at Bernie's.
So funny. The guy's
dead the whole time.
(CHUCKLES)
l haven't seen it.
Speaking of weekends,
you excited about
our date this weekend?
(lN SOUTHERN ACCENT)
Of course, Nathaniel.
Okay.
Where are you taking me?
Well. . .
(lN SOUTHERN ACCENT)
The finest steakhouse
in all Savannah.
Savannah? That's a far way
from Scranton.
Did you mean
a real date?
No.
Did you?
Totally not.
l thought
it was for real.
So l was excited,
but it was part
of the game.
You're sure it was water?
lt couldn't have been acid?
l already declared you,
it was too dark to tell !
Stop playing games
with me, Crawdad !
This is not a game!
This is my life!
You are
out of order, sir!
Answer me!
You are out of order!
l think Michael
may have snapped.
Or maybe he's just
stuck in character.
Well, which is worse?
Snapped or stuck?
Both.
They're both worse.
lt's gonna be all right.
We're a good company.
We'll figure this out.
We're not going under.
Jim, what if we both
lose our jobs?
l'm trying to think
of a way that this
all ends up fine,
and l can't
think of one.
Deb, what in the world?
Do you have the vapors?
Michael ! Not now.
Can't wait.
We have to get you
to our witch doctor
right now.
Come on, come on !
l should just go.
(lN SOUTHERN ACCENT)
Where to now, Caleb?
MlCHAEL:
To Mama Juju Booboo.
Michael, can l. . .
Okay, l'm just gonna
skip right past the
what and go with why?
Because this is
the recreation
of a crime scene.
l'm the dead body,
and these are my
brain chunks.
Hey, shut up.
You're dead.
Michael, can l talk
to you in your office?
No Michael here.
My name is. . .
Caleb!
Today, of all days?
No! You shut up!
They need this game, Jim.
Let us have this stupid
little game, all right?
(KNOCKlNG ON DOOR)
(lN SOUTHERN ACCENT)
Oh, you startled me!
My stars, my heart nearly
leapt out of my chest.
What can l do you for?
Wallace is on the phone.
He's returning your call.
Detective Wallace?
l don't think so.
l think it's David Wallace
from Dunder Mifflin.
Oh, shucks!
Tell him l'm not here.
You're not gonna
answer the phone?
No, l only answer
to Detective Wallace,
'cause l got a warm body
in the other room.
l'll take it.
Hey, David.
DAVID: Hey. Sorry to be
getting back to you guys
so late.
Things are stiII
a bit unclear.
We didn't officiaIIy
decide anything yet.
Oh, okay.
But if l can be candid
with you here, Jim,
it's not good.
We fuIIy expect
to be out of money
by the end of the year.
lnsolvent.
So, well, you know what?
I'm sorry. I have to run.
But we will
taIk soon, okay?
Sure.
Okay.
Oh, you know,
while l have you,
today l was
working on this pitch
for a supermarket chain. . .
Great.
. . .and it would
actually be a big account.
Okay, look,
you know what?
I can't reaIIy get my
head around anything
Iike that right now,
but that's great.
Keep after it,
but I gotta run.
Okay.
Thanks, Jim.
See you.
(CLEARS THROAT)
What's the news?
Nothing yet.
Well, l guess
that's not. . .
Well, there is
some bad news.
There has been
another murder.
A murder, you say?
l do declare.
Conference room, everyone.
Do we have to play?
No.
Super.
Oh, this could be
a juicy one.
Get in there!
JIM: I think today
was a good day to
have two managers,
because if you're a famiIy
stuck on a lifeboat
in the middle of the ocean,
one parent might want
to just keep rowing.
But if the other parent
wants to pIay a game,
it's not because
they're crazy.
lt's because they're
doing it for the kids.
And l get that now.
(lN SOUTHERN ACCENT)
There has been a lot of
murder and a lot of intrigue.
My little heart can
barely take it no more.
(NORMAL ACCENT) Today is
the hardest l have worked
in a long, long time.
l didn't do it!
Okay.
Everybody just
calm down.
l am calm.
Count of three,
we're all gonna
put down our guns.
l have crossbows.
We'll put down
our weaponry on
the count of three.
ANDY: Okay.
You ready?
DWlGHT: l'm ready.
One, two. . .
Two.
Three.
(ALL YELLlNG)
Andy revealed himself
to be a double agent,
at which point,
Dwight felt comfortable
revealing that he also
was a double agent,
and then,
Michael announced
to everybody that,
get this,
he was a double agent.
Oh, and it is 6:00.
Really?
lt wasn't me!
l'm not going
down for this!
Hey, l want
to go home.
Get the keys
out of my purse,
start the car.
(ALL PANTlNG)
(ALL YELLlNG)